property-system.com 2017-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Property Investment. Simplified | TycoonSystem

**PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF WEBSITE USE FOR  WWW.TYCOONSYSTEM.COM**

**Your Consent**

Below we set out our privacy policy which will govern the way in which we process any personal information that you provide to us. [We will notify you if the way in which we process your information is to change at any time].

IF YOU SUBMIT YOUR DETAILS TO US VIA THIS WEBSITE, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THEIR USE IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT ANY OF THESE TERMS, LEAVE THIS WEBSITE NOW.

Our details are : Vadesha Properties Limited, 4 Hatherleigh Road, Leicester, LE5 5NR, England. If you have any queries, please contact our managing director, Parmdeep Vadesha through our Contact Us page. You can access our home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data save information collected by cookies that we use (see below).

**Who may process data**

Your personal information (which includes your name, address and any other details you provide to us which concern you as an individual) may be shared by us with other members in our group and processed both by us and those other companies including www.1shoppingcart.com, www.salesforce.com, www.paypal.com. Our website also includes a link to www.1shoppingcart.comwww.salesforce.com, www.paypal.com and such companies may collect personal data about visitors to our site. Each of our group companies authorised to process your information as mentioned above will do so in accordance with this privacy policy.

The server on which your personal data is hosted is located in the EU.

BY PROVIDING YOUR DETAILS YOU WILL BE INDICATING YOUR CONSENT TO THE TRANSFER OF YOUR DATA TO THE COUNTRY/COUNTRIES SPECIFIED ABOVE.

**Purpose of processing**

We will use your information for the purpose of fulfilling orders placed by you, processing any other transactions authorised or made by you with us, informing you by email of special offers and providing other marketing information related to services or products which we think you may find of interest and undertaking product or customer research/development. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

BY PROVIDING YOUR DETAILS YOU WILL BE INDICATING YOUR CONSENT TO THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA FOR THESE PURPOSES.

Disclosure and Transfer of Your Information to a Third Party Purchasing Our Business In the event that we sell our business to a third party, we need your authority to transfer your details to that third party.

In the unlikely event that a liquidator, administrator or receiver is appointed over us or all or any part of our assets that insolvency practitioner may transfer your information to a third party purchaser of the business provided that purchaser undertakes to use your information for the same purposes as set out in this policy. Your information will not be disclosed to government or local authorities or other government institutions save as required by law or other binding regulations.

BY PROVIDING YOUR DETAILS YOU WILL BE INDICATING YOUR CONSENT TO THE TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA TO A THIRD PARTY PURCHASER

**Cookies**

We may send a small file to your computer when you visit our website. This will enable us to identify your computer, track your behaviour on our website and to identify your particular areas of interest so as to enhance your future visits to this website. We may use cookies to collect and store personal data and we link information stored by cookies with personal data you supply to us. Save for the use of cookies, we do not automatically log data or collect data save for information you specifically provide to us. You can set your computer browser to reject cookies but this may preclude your use of certain parts of this website.

**Security measures**

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorised access, improper use and disclosure, unauthorised destruction or accidental loss.

**Access to information**

You may ask us whether we are storing personal information about you by contacting us in Contact Us page and, if you wish and upon payment of a fee of £10, we will provide you with a copy of the personal data we hold about you by email. We may ask for proof of your identity before providing any information and reserve the right to refuse to provide information requested if identity is not established.

**Copyright**

All website design, text, graphics, the selection and arrangement thereof are Copyright © 2012, Vadesha Properties Limited, ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.

**Disclaimer of Warranty and Liability**

The following provisions may be curtailed or disallowed by the laws of certain jurisdictions. In such case, the terms hereof are to be read as excluding or limiting such term so as to satisfy such law. We do not represent or warrant that the information accessible via this website is accurate, complete or current. We have no liability whatsoever in respect of any use which you make of such information. The information provided on this website has not been written to meet your individual requirements and it is your sole responsibility to satisfy yourself prior to ordering any products or services from us that they are suitable for your purposes. Whilst we make all reasonable attempts to exclude viruses from the website, we cannot ensure such exclusion and no liability is accepted for viruses. Thus, you are recommended to take all appropriate safeguards before downloading information or images from this website. All warranties, express or implied, statutory or otherwise are hereby excluded. Neither we nor any of our employees or affiliated entities will be liable for any kind of damages and howsoever arising including, without limitation, loss of profits, compensatory, consequential, direct, exemplary, incidental, indirect, punitive or special, damages or any liability which you may have to a third party, even if we have been advised of the possibility of such loss. We are not responsible for the direct or indirect consequences of you linking to any other website from this website.

**Age Restriction**

This website is intended for use by those over the age of 18 years. No one under that age should carry out any activity whatsoever based on the information on this website. If you are under the age of 18 years please leave the site immediately.

**Geographic Restriction**

These terms and this disclaimer and any claim based on use of information from this website shall be governed by the laws of England and Wales and for our benefit you agree to submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of England.

**Enquiries**

If you have any enquiry or concern about our privacy policy or the way in which we are handling personal data please contact Parmdeep Vadesha through Contact Us page. If at any time you wish us to cease processing your information please send a message to Parmdeep Vadesha through Contact Us page and insert “unsubscribe” as the subject heading.

**Consent**

In order to access the information on this website, you must signal acceptance of the terms and disclaimer set out above by providing your name and email address in exchange for our free mini course. If you do not accept any of these terms, leave this website now.
